[{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd2"},"rt":42678,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190408,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd3"},"rt":51999,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242720,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd4"},"rt":43406,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286435,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd5"},"rt":23438,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":310181,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd6"},"rt":49305,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359799,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd7"},"rt":20366,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380470,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd8"},"rt":10813,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391592,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fd9"},"rt":106238,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498143,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fda"},"rt":29300,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528602,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fdb"},"rt":24460,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553392,"subject":"JUXWY","study":"SGCX","session":"62ce0bc0eb0f80b9f63dfcb6","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5cbb78d664170f00011d7c4f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88feb"},"rt":25791,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":109057,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AMJ J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fec"},"rt":13508,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122638,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fed"},"rt":78657,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":201502,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"6B B B F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fee"},"rt":37152,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":238902,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"2J J I I E E I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88fef"},"rt":6956,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245942,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88ff0"},"rt":10930,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256950,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88ff1"},"rt":11544,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268566,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88ff2"},"rt":9974,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":278614,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88ff3"},"rt":7934,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286622,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c88ff4"},"rt":16327,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303022,"subject":"LWKFA","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf1403969ed71063834d40","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"629224cea1460101a9847de2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"02 PMX X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89004"},"rt":186587,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":301600,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E 09 AM08 AMI J J J J J 05 PML A A B C O O O D N C E F F F G G H I I J J J K N 06 PMG K K K K P A E L E E E G G G C C H C H F F Z Z Z I B B B O J J X X N N D M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89005"},"rt":252868,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554735,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"M M M A A B C D E F F G G H I J J K K L M M N N N N N G O O O P C J J Z O D D D E E F F G H I J J J K K K L L M M N B O X P H Z Z X X X D D D F I J H N M M M N N N N O O Z Z X F I F J B F F F M N N N N O Z Z X X X O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89006"},"rt":104368,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":659372,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"K K K 7L B B B B F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89007"},"rt":65299,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":724947,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J I E E E K A A E L L K K A F F F B B B B F B B E E E E I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89008"},"rt":29270,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":754479,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,Z","hovered":"F F X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89009"},"rt":25157,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":779731,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM02 PM01 PMM M L L M M L L L M M 12 PMM M M M M B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8900a"},"rt":16119,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":795934,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"X F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8900b"},"rt":18971,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":814992,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B B Z Z 02 PMF F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8900c"},"rt":12715,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":827794,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"4X X X X X X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8900d"},"rt":20701,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":848563,"subject":"RZNOS","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29df4cc45015ee5b3918","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5f2280c4a4474574b3704136","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8901d"},"rt":11422,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":37088,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8901e"},"rt":12602,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":50016,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8901f"},"rt":76496,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126840,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"8G H H B B B F E X F F E E E E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89020"},"rt":35282,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":162509,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B F E B B B B E I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89021"},"rt":22510,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185348,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F F B B M M B E F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89022"},"rt":49933,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235589,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"09 AM10 AM12 PMB B F I I J J M M M G O O X X G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89023"},"rt":24445,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260432,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"5F F F F B B B M M E G G G A A K K L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89024"},"rt":37847,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":298601,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z H H L O O X X C G G A F F B B M M M M E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89025"},"rt":8307,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307298,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AM03 PMX X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89026"},"rt":18693,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326328,"subject":"SPNB1","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf142e53d76bed98deee5f","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a78e410ae9a0b0001a97274","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PMX K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89036"},"rt":24045,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":60937,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E E G E G G G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89037"},"rt":56492,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117495,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"2B J F F B B B F G C H Z M M J 2X C C C C C C H H H X X X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89038"},"rt":28001,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145556,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J J J E G G G C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89039"},"rt":38961,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":184578,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J I I E E E B B B E F F B B M M M M J I I I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8903a"},"rt":14621,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199260,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F B B B B F E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8903b"},"rt":17537,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216857,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":"B 02 PM01 PM12 PMB F F C P L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8903c"},"rt":8383,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":225300,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8903d"},"rt":23022,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":248382,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"44X Z Z N Z F F F F B B B F F F E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8903e"},"rt":19602,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268045,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM02 PM03 PMC C G F F F X X X X G A E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8903f"},"rt":30382,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298489,"subject":"C1OGM","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf141318ee255f76deee46","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5dd663c3cf8e7e5efc123950","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"G G G G G G C C C C X X X X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8904f"},"rt":17566,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":50433,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E 608 AM09 AM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89050"},"rt":16807,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":67292,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"G C X X 02 PM01 PMM B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89051"},"rt":70258,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137600,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,O","hovered":"F 12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB J J J X 05 PM02 PMB X O 2112 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89052"},"rt":37581,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":175385,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F N N 04 PM10 AMJ I I I 10 AM10 AMI E E E E E E E E M M F 7E E E B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89053"},"rt":36836,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212279,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F B B B B B 301 PMF F F O Z Z O B B J J M M X X X X E 6E G G A G G G G L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89054"},"rt":24444,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236767,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM12 PMM 12 PM01 PMX X X O O C H H L 7P K A A A G G N N Z Z Z H H H L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89055"},"rt":29713,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266527,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PM11 AMM F F F F B B B J J I M X X G G G A L L L L L L K P P C H C C G B B B O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89056"},"rt":22615,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":289191,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMN Z O O O O X B B B B B F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89057"},"rt":22501,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311740,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PMX M O F F F E G G G A A A L L O O X X X X O B B F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89058"},"rt":24919,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":336704,"subject":"O9F0G","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf29dab1478c4d5d00b347","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"5a4ffdf876d1c60001aa945a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"12 PM12 PM09 AM12 PM03 PMX X X X C C C G H H 10K A A H X X X X L H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89068"},"rt":89247,"condition":"32321","q":6,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":132595,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"B B F C C G E A L H O O Z N N D L L P K A E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89069"},"rt":83396,"condition":"32321","q":7,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216310,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F B B B F B B I J J M M X N N N D D M J J I I B B F X X X O O X H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8906a"},"rt":47162,"condition":"32321","q":8,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263801,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"H H B F F G G G L G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8906b"},"rt":58377,"condition":"32321","q":9,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":322290,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"M J B B B B M M I I B I E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8906c"},"rt":17375,"condition":"32321","q":10,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339779,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F E E F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8906d"},"rt":19281,"condition":"32321","q":11,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359187,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8906e"},"rt":12578,"condition":"32321","q":12,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371877,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c8906f"},"rt":16820,"condition":"32321","q":13,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388873,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z 03 PM02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89070"},"rt":8452,"condition":"32321","q":14,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397509,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMX X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62d83e630a7aae4618c89071"},"rt":24063,"condition":"32321","q":15,"explicit":"3","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"2","ixn":"1","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":421735,"subject":"TF3PK","study":"SGCX","session":"62cf10a55b7a4edf23d9af26","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62ce044e6c67e74262f4b635","sona_id":"615a084387075364a7462335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"B 07 PM07 PM06 PMX X K "}]
